<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aesop Fables</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="AesopsFables"> </string>

    <string name="btn">Story 1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_avariciousand_envious">AvariciousandEnvious</string>
    <string name="btn1" />
    <string name="HerculesandtheWaggoner">HerculesandtheWaggoner</string>
    <string name="btn2">Story 3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheAntandtheGrasshopper">TheAntandtheGrasshopper</string>
    <string name="btn3">story4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheAssandtheLapdog">TheAssandtheLapdog</string>/>
    <string name="btn4">story5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheAssandtheCharger">TheAssandtheCharger</string>
    <string name="btn5">story6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheAsstheFoxandtheLion">TheAsstheFoxandtheLion</string>
    <string name="btn6">story7</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheAssintheLionsSkin">TheAssintheLionsSkin</string>
    <string name="btn7">story8</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheAsssBrains">TheAsssBrains</string>
    <string name="btn8">story9</string>
    <string name="title_activity_TheBaldManandtheFly">TheBaldManandtheFly</string>/>
    <string name="btn9">story10</string>
   <string name="title_activity_TheBattheBirdsandtheBeasts">TheBattheBirdsandtheBeastsy</string>/


    <string name="story1">Two neighbours came before Jupiter and prayed him to grant their hearts desire. Now the one was full of avarice, and the other eaten up with envy.

So to punish them both, Jupiter granted that each might have whatever he wished for himself, but only on condition that his neighbour had twice as much.

The Avaricious man prayed to have a room full of gold.

No sooner said than done; but all his joy was turned to grief when he found that his neighbour had two rooms full of the precious metal.

Then came the turn of the Envious man, who could not bear to think that his neighbour had any joy at all.

So he prayed that he might have one of his own eyes put out, by which means his companion would become totally blind.

 </string>
    <string name="story2">A Waggoner was once driving a heavy load along a very muddy way.

At last he came to a part of the road where the wheels sank half-way into the mire, and the more the horses pulled, the deeper sank the wheels.

So the Waggoner threw down his whip, and knelt down and prayed to Hercules the Strong.

"O Hercules, help me in this my hour of distress," quoth he.

But Hercules appeared to him, and said:

"Tut, man, don't sprawl there. Get up and put your shoulder to the wheel.
    </string>
    <string name="story3">In a field one summers day a Grasshopper was hopping about, chirping and singing to its hearts content. An Ant passed by, bearing along with great toil an ear of corn he was taking to the nest.

"Why not come and chat with me," said the Grasshopper, "instead of toiling and moiling in that way?"

"I am helping to lay up food for the winter," said the Ant, "and recommend you to do the same."

"Why bother about winter?" said the Grasshopper; "we have got plenty of food at present."

But the Ant went on its way and continued its toil.

When the winter came the Grasshopper had no food and found itself dying of hunger, while it saw the ants distributing every day corn and grain from the stores they had collected in the summer.

Then the Grasshopper knew: It is best to prepare for the days of necessity.</string>
    <string name="story4">A Farmer one day came to the stables to see to his beasts of burden: among them was his favourite Ass, that was always well fed and often carried his master.

With the Farmer came his Lapdog, who danced about and licked his hand and frisked about as happy as could be.

The Farmer felt in his pocket, gave the Lapdog some dainty food, and sat down while he gave his orders to his servants.

The Lapdog jumped into his masters lap, and lay there blinking while the Farmer stroked his ears.

The Ass, seeing this, broke loose from his halter and commenced prancing about in imitation of the Lapdog.

The Farmer could not hold his sides with laughter, so the Ass went up to him, and putting his feet upon the Farmers shoulder attempted to climb into his lap.

The Farmers servants rushed up with sticks and pitchforks and soon taught the Ass that: Clumsy jesting is no joke.

 </string>
    <string name="story5">An Ass congratulated a Horse on being so ungrudgingly and carefully provided for, while he himself had scarcely enough to eat, nor even that without hard work.

But when war broke out, the heavy armed soldier mounted the Horse, and rushed into the very midst of the enemy, and the Horse, being wounded, fell dead on the battle-field.

Then the Ass, seeing all these things, changed his mind, and commiserated the Horse, saying: "How much more fortunate am I than a charger. I can remain at home in safety while he is exposed to all the perils of war."

 </string>
    <string name="story6">The Ass and the Fox, having entered into a partnership together, went out into the forest to hunt.

They had not proceeded far, when they met a Lion.

The Fox approached the Lion and promised to contrive for him the capture of the Ass, if he would pledge his word that his own life should be spared.

On his assuring him that he would not injure him, the Fox led the Ass to a deep pit, and contrived that he should fall into it.

The Lion, seeing that the Ass was secured, immediately clutched the Fox, and then attacked the Ass at his leisure.
    </string>
    <string name="story7">An Ass once found a Lions skin which the hunters had left out in the sun to dry.

He put it on and went towards his native village.

All fled at his approach, both men and animals, and he was a proud Ass that day.

In his delight he lifted up his voice and brayed, but then every one knew him, and his owner came up and gave him a sound cudgelling for the fright he had caused.

And shortly afterwards a Fox came up to him and said:

Ah, I knew you by your voice
    </string>
    <string name="story8">The Lion and the Fox went hunting together.

The Lion, on the advice of the Fox, sent a message to the Ass, proposing to make an alliance between their two families.

The Ass came to the place of meeting, overjoyed at the prospect of a royal alliance.

But when he came there the Lion simply pounced on the Ass, and said to the Fox: 

"Here is our dinner for to-day. Watch you here while I go and have a nap. Woe betide you if you touch my prey." 

The Lion went away and the Fox waited; but finding that his master did not return, ventured to take out the brains of the Ass and ate them up.

When the Lion came back he soon noticed the absence of the brains, and asked the Fox in a terrible voice:

"What have you done with the brains?"

"Brains, your Majesty! it had none, or it would never have fallen into your trap."

 </string>
    <string name="story9">There was once a Bald Man who sat down after work on a hot summers day.

A Fly came up and kept buzzing about his bald pate, and stinging him from time to time.

The Man aimed a blow at his little enemy, but his palm came on his head instead.

Again the Fly tormented him, but this time the Man was wiser and said:

"You will only injure yourself if you take notice of despicable enemies
    </string>
    <string name="story10">A great conflict was about to come off between the Birds and the Beasts.

When the two armies were collected together the Bat hesitated which to join.

The Birds that passed his perch said:

"Come with us"; but he said: "I am a Beast."

Later on, some Beasts who were passing underneath him looked up and said:

"Come with us"; but he said: "I am a Bird."

Luckily at the last moment peace was made, and no battle took place, so the Bat came to the Birds and wished to join in the rejoicings, but they all turned against him and he had to fly away.

He then went to the Beasts, but soon had to beat a retreat, or else they would have torn him to pieces.

"Ah," said the Bat, "I see now, He that is neither one thing nor the other has no friends."

 </string>


    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="title_activity_herculesandthe_waggoner">HerculesandtheWaggoner</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_antandthe_grasshopper">TheAntandtheGrasshopper</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assandthe_lapdog">TheAssandtheLapdog</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assandthe_charger">TheAssandtheCharger</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assthe_foxandthe_lion">TheAsstheFoxandtheLion</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_assinthe_lions_skin">TheAssintheLionsSkin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_asss_brains">TheAsssBrains</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_bald_manandthe_fly">TheBaldManandtheFly</string>
    <string name="title_activity_the_batthe_birdsandthe_beasts">TheBattheBirdsandtheBeasts</string>

</resources>
